snapgene.com 2019-09-03

# Privacy Policy - SnapGene

This site is owned and operated by GSL Biotech LLC. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

**Personal Information that GSL Biotech May Collect Online**  
GSL Biotech collects personal information online, including names, e-mail addresses, and billing information. This information is collected when voluntarily provided by users making purchases, subscribing to our newsletter, requesting assistance, providing feedback, or participating in our user forum.

GSL Biotech collects identifying information about devices that use SnapGene software for software licensing purposes. GSL Biotech collects IP addresses from visitors to the websites snapgene.com and www.snapgene.com.

GSL Biotech does not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 16. In addition, no part of our website is designed with the purpose of attracting any person under age 16.

**How GSL Biotech Uses Personal Information Collected Online**  
Unless you otherwise consent, we will use your personal information only for the purpose for which it is submitted, such as to reply to your communications, to process billing and business requests, and to provide the newsletter.

**How GSL Biotech Shares Personal Information Collected Online**  
GSL Biotech does not share any personal information collected online with any outside parties, with the exception of billing information shared with the third-party credit card processor when processing payments, and sales-related correspondence shared with our local distributors.

**Cookies and Security**  
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. GSL Biotech uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. You can still use the general website if your browser is set to reject cookies, though some features of the account management page may not function properly with cookies disabled. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you.

**Compliance with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**  
GSL Biotech extends the protections required by the GDRP to all users regardless of location. Specifically, in addition to the policies listed above:

  * GSL Biotech does not engage in profiling or indirect collection of data.
  * Data is retained for as long as needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected.
  * You have a right to request a copy of your personal data.
  * You have a right to correct your personal data if they are incomplete or inaccurate.
  * Upon your request, we will erase your personal data unless required by law not to do so.

Please direct any questions relating to our data collection policies to [info@snapgene.com](mailto:info@snapgene.com).

**Location Data**  
This site includes IP2Location LITE data available from [http://lite.ip2location.com](http://lite.ip2location.com/).

All areas on this website that may involve the transmittal of personal information, such as purchase pages and account management pages, are configured to send and receive information only over secure connections.
